<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MergeX App</title>
    <link>https://mergex.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MergeX App</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:57:56 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mergex.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The creation story of Merge</title>
      <link>https://mergex.app/blog/a-new-year-a-new-website-introducing-apsho-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 12:57:56 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mergex.app/blog/a-new-year-a-new-website-introducing-apsho-1/</guid>
      <description>Hi, nice to meet you, my name is mengdi, I&amp;rsquo;m from Beijing, China and I&amp;rsquo;m the product manager/designer/developer of Merge App. Merge is a product I spent two years creating by myself full time, and it&amp;rsquo;s my biggest dream since I chose to be a developer - to create a self-approved work by myself independently. As you can see, part of my dream has come true. During these two years, I encountered a lot of difficulties and had thoughts of giving up, but I persevered and finally realized my small wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Notes</title>
      <link>https://mergex.app/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mergex.app/license/</guid>
      <description>License and Open Source Notes Down The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright (c) 2016 Rob Phillips.
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mergex.app/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mergex.app/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Merge Privacy Policy Welcome to Merge, a freely configurable, modular efficiency tool. You can create your own home page that focuses on what matters most in the moment, according to your needs.
1. The information we collect We do not use any third-party tools to collect any of your data. In Merge, all the data you create yourself is stored securely in your iCloud account or device storage. In short, you can produce content in Merge without worrying about data security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://mergex.app/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mergex.app/terms/</guid>
      <description>These Terms of Service apply to your access to and use of the Merge application, so please read them carefully. By logging in to the Service, you are deemed to have fully agreed to the terms of this Agreement.
Acceptance of Terms By accessing or using the Service, you are agreeing to be bound by all of the following terms. Therefore, please read all of them carefully before using the Service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
